(Penny:)Almost as dirty as the dirty girl
who's wearing them.
(Penny:)Okay, that's enough.
(Leonard:)-Disagree.
-Keep going.
(Penny:)So, what do you think?
(Sheldon:)A tad asymmetrical,
but nothing to be concerned about.
(Penny:)Please, Sheldon. I need you.
To. .. what?
(Penny:)To take me.
(Sheldon:)I'm not taking you anywhere
till you put on a shirt.
(Penny:)Come on, Sheldon.
You and me right here.
(Sheldon:)Penny, for the thousandth time,
(Sheldon:)I'm saving myself
for someone special.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps a cute
bespectacled neuroscientist
(Sheldon:)with hair the color of mud.
(Penny:)I think I know how
to change your mind.
(Penny:)-That's enough.
(Stuart:)I was okay with it.